

"DWIC is never enough!"

Summary _

Current Computer Science Undergraduate at UNSW. Experience in digital signal processing, quantum computing and natural language processing. Research interests lie in question answering, language model and vision-language grounding. Super nerd who loves Python, C++ and Linux and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Work Experience _____

IT, Monash Melbourne, Australia

TEACHING ASSISTANT Mar, 2021 - Present

• FIT5217: Natural language processing: 21S1

CSE, UNSW Sydney, Australia

Feb. 2021 - Present

Dec, 2020 - Feb, 2021

Dec, 2020 - Feb, 2021

May, 2020 - Present

RESEARCH STUDENT, SUPERVISED BY Lizhen Qu AND Lina Yao

· Self-proposed research project: Visual Commonsense Reasoning in Complex Events Detection

Harrison.ai Sydney, Australia

Applied Al scientist intern, Supervised by Ben Hachey

• Develop AI algorithms, prototypes and solutions for **Prioritization of patients' CT Brain reports.**

Linked entity fuzzy search via sense2vec + SciSpacy + stanza + FastText

Contextual word semantic search via domain adaptive DistilBERT in an unsupervised fashion

Mean pooling sentence semantic search via domain adaptive DistilBERT in an unsupervised fashion

Sentence semantic search via BioSentVec + FastText

Sentence semantic search via DistilBERT (with BERT-flow)

Anserini+BM25+RM3+SBERT cross-encoder

Data61, CSIRO Remote

EXTERNAL RESEARCH STUDENT, ADVISED BY Conrad Sanderson, Work with Jason Rumenagan

• PyArmadillo, a API library of Armadillo using Python-C++ bindings

Write and design under the product development flow with the Data61 vacation scholar.

Open-source minimum viable product(MVP) at the first stage.

Monash Univeristy Remote

RESEARCH ASSISTANT, SUPERVISED BY Reza Haffari AND Lizhen Qu

 Project: Commonsense Reasoning Question Answering Apply ProphetNet as the backbone for the model trained on ATOMIC data.

Evaluate the proposed model results.

Co-authored a long paper accepted by COLING 2020.

Co-authored a short paper submitted ACL 2021.

• Project: Construction of a Multimodal Procedural Knowledge Base for Action Planning

Design and collect crowdsourcing data via Amazon Mechanical Turk.

Design the baseline and propose a multimodal action planning model via the knowledge base.

A long paper for ICCV 2021 is in preparation.

TERRY YUE ZHUO · RÉSUMÉ FEBRUARY 23, 2021

UNSW Sydney Sydney, Australia

CASUAL ACADEMIC/TUTOR/COURSE ADMIN

ENGG1000: Introduction to Engineering Design and Innovation:

20T1, 20T3(100% student satisfaction), 21T1

• **ELEC2134**: Circuits and Signals:

The only undergraduate in the team while remains are PhDs. 20T1, 20T3, 21T1

• **COMP1010**: The Art of Computing:

21T1(Backup)

• COMP1531: Software Engineering Fundamentals:

• COMP2521: Data Structures and Algorithms:

21T1

COMP9020: Foundations of Computer Science* (Graduate Course):

21T1(Run consultations for all 200 graduate students)

• **COMP9021**: Principles of Programming* (**Graduate Course**):

21T1(Run tutorials for all 250 graduate students)

• COMP9024: Data Structures and Algorithms* (Graduate Course):

21T1(Course Admin, run labs for all 200 graduate students)

Quantum Computation and Communication Technology (CQC2T), UNSW Sydney

Sydney, Australia

Feb, 2020 - Present

Nov, 2019 - Sep, 2020

RESEARCH STUDENT, SUPERVISED BY Arne Laucht

- Propose a research project of digitizing the lock-in amplifier in MATLAB.
- · Propose the implementation structure of the digitizing lock-in amplifier in the team's quantum computing system.

Microsoft Shanghai, China

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

Dec, 2019 - Feb, 2020

- Apply Azure SQL DB/DW, Azure Data Lake Storage, Azure Data Lake Analytics, Azure Machine Learning, Stream Analytics, Azure Data Factory, or Cosmos DB to companies' data.
- Design cloud architecture for top tier companies.

Project

PyArmadillo Data61

Dec, 2020 - Present CO-LEAD DEVELOPER

- Design and develop the Cube class in PyArmadillo.
- Validate the performance of the library.
- Write the user document.
- Design the tests.

Off-world Robotics Project, Vertically Integrated Project

UNSW Sydney

RESEARCHER

Feb., 2020 - Dec., 2020

- · Determine the constraints of our embedded systems, sourcing embedded boards for use on the prototype rovers, and testing them with an RTOS or scheduling architecture.
- · Research existing approaches to the SLAM problem, comparing them, and proposing a SLAM system for use on the rovers.

Py Googletrans Github

CONTRIBUTOR, COLLABORATOR May, 2020 - Present

· Googletrans: Free and Unlimited Google translate API for Python. Translates totally free of charge.

Education

POWER ENGINEER

UNSW Sydney (University of New South Wales)

Sydney, Australia

Oct, 2019 - Dec, 2020

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING (MINOR IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING)

Jul. 2018 - Sep. 2021(Expected)

• Weighed Average Mark 86.3, Top 3% in Faculty of Engineering

Extracurricular Activity _____

BLUESAT UNSW Sydney

• Working on the satellite project which will be launched in 2021-2022.

- Supervising in MPPT board testing and designing.

FEBRUARY 23, 2021 TERRY YUE ZHUO · RÉSUMÉ **ELSOC UNSW UNSW Sydney**

ACADEMIC TUTOR, SUB-COMMITTEE MEMBER

May. 2019 - Present • Ran crashcourses (lectures) where more than twenty students on average attended.

Publication

PyArmadillo: an alternative approach to linear algebra in Python

Technical Report, Data61/CSIRO

JASON RUMENGAN, **TERRY YUE ZHUO**, CONRAD SANDERSON

Neural Symbolic Commonsense Reasoner with Relation Predictors

ACL 2021

SUBMITTED TO ACL 2021

In Submission

COSMO: Conditional SEQ2SEQ-based Mixture Model for Zero-Shot Commonsense **Question Answering**

COLING 2020

Farhad Moghimifar, Lizhen Qu, **Yue Zhuo**, Mahsa Baktashmotlagh and Gholamreza Haffari

Oct, 2020

Honors & Awards

2019	Dean's Honours List (Highly Commended), Top 2% of UNSW Engineering	Sydney
2019	Taste of Research scholarships Recipient (A\$5,000), TOP 12 of UNSW Engineering	Sydney
2020	Taste of Research scholarships Recipient (A\$6,000), TOP 43 of UNSW Engineering	Sydney

Service

2021	Volunteer, AAAI 2021	Online
2020	Volunteer, EMNLP 2020	Online
2020	Volunteer, NeurIPS 2020	Online
2020	Volunteer, WiNLP 2020	Seattle, WA

FEBRUARY 23, 2021 TERRY YUE ZHUO · RÉSUMÉ